<item>
	<title>What About Bob?</title>
	<link>
	<sublink>https://streamango.com/embed/tceqtccblerplkdn/ (Streamango)</sublink>
	<sublink>https://www.rapidvideo.com/e/FTVX8DIFAZ (Rapidvideo)</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ofS4QdCL01iRy3p9hUkErsRfcxE.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/gZGlD5sNnBjNrrmiwdnGB4Ik34U.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>Before going on vacation, self-involved psychiatrist Dr. Leo Marvin has the misfortune of taking on a new patient: Bob Wiley. An exemplar of neediness and a compendium of phobias, Bob follows Marvin to his family's country house. Dr. Marvin tries to get him to leave; the trouble is, everyone loves Bob. As his oblivious patient makes himself at home, Dr. Marvin loses his professional composure and, before long, may be ready for the loony bin himself.</summary>
</item>

<item>
	<title>The Nun</title>
	<link>
	<sublink>https://streamango.com/embed/sdqcqdkflpmqonss/ (Streamango)</sublink>
	<sublink>https://www.rapidvideo.com/e/FTL4EZ45MX (Rapidvideo)</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/7cNG3dCBY4fWol63eJSykFX6DnT.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ndGAaJj9jRrAYEYcCVCD2qoCS7Q.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>When a young nun at a cloistered abbey in Romania takes her own life, a priest with a haunted past and a novitiate on the threshold of her final vows are sent by the Vatican to investigate. Together they uncover the order’s unholy secret. Risking not only their lives but their faith and their very souls, they confront a malevolent force in the form of the same demonic nun that first terrorized audiences in “The Conjuring 2,” as the abbey becomes a horrific battleground between the living and the damned.</summary>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Predator</title>
	<link>
	<sublink>https://streamango.com/embed/kfrnqqkeakerddkq/ (Streamango)</sublink>
	<sublink>https://www.rapidvideo.com/e/FWKLBTQ2WK (Rapidvideo)</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/ofS4QdCL01iRy3p9hUkErsRfcxE.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/original/5XOPHVAQMyRkUqSlbmZ361rJO6y.jpg</fanart>
	<summary>From the outer reaches of space to the small-town streets of suburbia, the hunt comes home. Now, the universe’s most lethal hunters are stronger, smarter and deadlier than ever before, having genetically upgraded themselves with DNA from other species. When a young boy accidentally triggers their return to Earth, only a ragtag crew of ex-soldiers and a disgruntled science teacher can prevent the end of the human race.</summary>
</item>